Acne is a condition cause by the overproduction of sebum oil which lubricates the skin and hair.
I'm Jackie with how to eliminate acne.
When the skin's pores become clogged with sebum, pimples can form.
To reduce acne and care for your skin, wash no more than twice a day with warm water and a mild cleanser specially formulated for oily skin or acne.
Try over the counter benzoyl peroxide products if you have pimples.
You can get them at the drug store.
Wash your hands often and try to keep them away from your face.
For girls, wash your make-up brushes and sponges often.
Talk to your doctor if your acne is serious or you're unable to control it.
For a natural solution, try baking soda.
Wet your skin and pour about two tablespoons of baking soda into your palm, add enough water to make a paste, apply the paste to your face in light circular motions for about a minute and rinse well with clean, lukewarm water, pat lightly to dry, and apply a benzoyl peroxide product only to the blemishes, allow that to dry and dab a little of the baking soda paste to the spots, leave it on overnight.
Remember, to clear acne, wash your face twice a day, use a baking soda paste, and check with your doctor for serious conditions.
I'm Jackie with how to eliminate acne.
You're looking good.